Get ready to watch what happened in the Anointing Water Revival in the UK
at the Troxy Theatre, London, UK, prayer line.
What have you done to this body?
Leave it!
Go away!
Stop it! Leave me alone!
What have you done to this lady?
I don't like you; go away!
How long have you been in this body?
Shut up!
No!
I hate her.
Why do you hate her?
She's a dirty whore.
Okay?
You don't know.
What have you done to her body?
Leave me alone!
I don't like you.
Get away from me.
What have you done?
Stop it!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I need to go home.
I want to go home.
Leave me alone.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Be free, in Jesus' name!
You evil spirit, you will leave, in Jesus' name!
You will leave, in Jesus' name!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Madam, you are declared free, in Jesus' name.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You so much!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Madam, we welcome you today here to the Anointing Revival in the UK.
We want to listen to your wonderful testimony that has been restored in your life.
Can you start by telling us your name and where you are from.
Hi, I'm Maggie Geddes. I'm from Southhampton (UK).
You are very welcome here today.
Can you tell us before you share your experience of what happened when you came,
what were the problems that you were experiencing in your life before your deliverance?
My problem started when I was a child.
I was abused mentally, physically, emotionally and sexually.
Throughout life, I grew up hating myself, the world and everybody.
I had anger and depression really badly because as I was abused,
I suffered from anger inside because I could not fight it.
It got deeper and deeper.
I then got depressed and started taking drugs.
I abused myself in every kind of way.
I started to try and kill myself a few times - suicide.
I have six children. I was very controlling.
I was very, very angry at my children.
I was really angry at myself but I took my anger out on them.
Apart from this depression that you mentioned
that brought about suicidal thoughts and this spirit of anger,
was there any other problem you were also experiencing
when you were moving alone, walking in parks?
What were the kind of problems you were experiencing?
I was absolutely petrified of the dark.
I would not leave my house in the dark.
I would not let my children go out in the dark.
I would never be alone in the dark.
I could not sleep at night in the dark; I had to have my television on all night.
I had to have sound. I could never be alone in the dark.
So you were extremely afraid of the dark and you were having a severe spirit of fear.
Can you tell us - this fear that you were experiencing, what did it push you to do?
It pushed me to try and kill myself, to be very angry,
hate everybody and really hate myself.
Apart from that side of your life, what about your physical health?
What were the experiences you were having?
I suffered from heart disease, lung disease, diabetes and all kinds of things.
Ok. So we can really hear the story of this sister,
how she was suffering from several different problems in her life.
She said, right from an early age, she had a severe fear of many different things in her life
which caused her depression, and this depression also caused her to have suicidal thoughts.
Because of that, she also started a drug abuse,
and she was just abusing herself both spirit, soul and body throughout her life
which also caused a lot of physical problems in her life.
So now we want to hear from you, as you came to the Anointing Water Revival,
you had all these problems that you were experiencing,
your children had been suffering from it, your family, relations.
Just explain to us - how did these problems now bring you to the Anointing Water Revival
in the UK, which was in London a couple of weeks ago?
And when you came there, the Anointing Water was administered to you.
Can you just explain to us - when you came there, what happened?
When I got there, I was quite surprised. I didn't know what I was expecting.
I came to the front for prayer and I didn't believe it.
I had doubts as to whether it was real or not.
I thought, "No, these people are all faking it!"
I did; I'm sorry. I thought everybody was faking it.
It came to my turn but I kept skipping it by swapping with other people.
Eventually an evangelist came to me and said,
"I annoint you with the Anointing Water" and I said, "Yeah".
As far as I was concerned, he sprayed me twice and I fell on the floor.
I woke up from the floor and somebody told me,
"Congratulations, you have been set free".
I said, "Thank you very much" but I had no idea what he was talking about.
I said, "Thank you, that's really great".
On my way home, as I had come with some people from Southamption from my church,
an elderly man said to me,
"You kind of reminded me of a silver-backed gorilla - really angry!"
I said, "Thanks, that's nice" but I still had no idea of what they were talking about.
Last Sunday, I went to church and a man from church said to me,
"I watched you on the internet".
I thought, "Oh, no!" He said, "You're on YouTube
and I thought, "This can't be true!"
He sent me the link and I went on YouTube and there I was.
Testimony Time
There I was for the whole world to see.
What I need to express to people is the way I feel -
overly joyous, happy, content and no fear of the dark.
Can we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
If you believe that Jesus Christ will work in your life today as well,
put your hands together for Jesus!
Testimony Time
So can you just explain now - after you received the deliverance
as you came to the Anointing Water Revival in the UK,
and you were administered upon with the Anointing Water,
how has your life been for the past few weeks?
It has been amazing, absolutely amazing!
I sleep like a baby; I have no fear of the dark.
I went through a park the other day at five o'clock in the evening with a little torch and nothing else.
I can't express how happy I am, how free I am.
I am now free!
Put your hands together for Jesus!
Testimony Time
There is no more anger, just joy and happiness.
I am content; I am actually content with my life.
Wow, glory be to Jesus Christ.
We thank God for this wonderful testimony that has been restored in your life.
And now, finally, there are many people out there,
they find themselves in depression, with suicidal thoughts,
many people find themselves very angry, fear, nightmares,
very similar challenges to the ones you were experiencing.
They too are looking for a solution.
Could you just give a word of advice to the people watching you right now?
Guys, you are here today. Come to the front.
Get that anointed prayer; it will change your life forever.
It changed mine, it can change all of you.
Testimony Time
And finally, we can see something in your hand.
That is the Anointing Water that was used,
that was the medium that God Almighty used to express Himself in your life.
Can you just tell us now - what is your word of advice about this Anointing Water?
This is the most amazing water you can ever get.
There will never be water like it.
You need to come to the front and be anointed with this Anointing Water.
Definitely.
Wow, glory be to Jesus Christ.
Can we once again put our hands together for Jesus!
Testimony Time
Power in the name of Jesus. Amen.
Glory be to Jesus Christ.
Once again, we also want to stress the fact,
as we have listened to this testimony now,
some people might be here, they are wondering what actually happened on the screen.
We want to stress the fact that what you saw on the screen of the television
when this lady was talking and saying different things,
and she was under the influence of the Holy Spirit, it was not her talking.
It was the evil spirit that was talking.
And you are seeing the evidence today.
Now she is standing here to the glory of God.
We can all see the difference in her face.
She is happy and we thank God that the best is yet to come for you, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Thank You, Lord!
Maggie Geddes - Southampton, UK
We are still listening to more wonderful testimonies.
Before you go, we want to encourage you once again.
Make His Word the standard for your life
and make sure that the name of Jesus Christ is glorified in your life
so that all the wonderful testimonies you have, will continue to be maintained
and multiplied in your life more and more, from glory to glory, in Jesus' name.
By the power of the Lord. Amen.
Anointing Water Revival - Birmingham, UK
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.